Yes, sir.
Okay sir.
Thank you sir!
{What happened is a matter of settlement
let them settle the matter.}
Yes sir!
Yes sir,
How?
All my friend said was true,
and what I did to my family.
The things I did to my family are all true.
My name is Chidiebere Agba
and this is my family.
I'm a native of a Anambra state,
Nigeria.
Last week Sunday, the man of God
came to me and prophesied that
I shouldn't surrender, that is all about settlement.
He also said I am at fault.
{You shouldn't surrender just like that.
Its too quick for you to just say no!
you have surrendered. Okay?
Thank you sir,
What happened is a matter of settlement
let them settle the matter.
Thank you sir.
Yes, sir!
Which is true.
I've grown up to be a sadist
among the society,
but when the force come,
I can't control myself.
It all started when I was in Madona;
a missionary school.
My intention was to go to that school
afterwards, I would go into a convent.
But when I entered I met other things inside the school.
As a missionary school, we were not meant to go out,
but we always jumped the fence and go clubbing;
that's when I was in my SS1
We clubbed from there, and that was when we started
clubbing and hanging out with
university graduates.
Before I graduated from Madonna,
me and one of my friend,
we never like seeing people happy.
Whenever we see some friends talking,
my friend would call me and ask, "why are these girls
they eating and going to the canteen together?"
Then, they wouldn't say anything,
but everything runs into my mind
I'll call one of them out, and say some things
if she's not buying to my idea, I will leave.
Some weeks after I would go to the friends corner,
any night when I want to ease myself,
I must penetrate people's corner.
I'll take what belongs to one friend,
and plant in the other girl's bag.
and lock it bag.
And then I happen to be a prefect in the school.
I started handling posts in my SS3
Then I was the assistant social prefect,
when they call for prefect meeting,
I'll make a suggestion,
and that suggestion goes to my plan.
Went the person is found out
she's being disgraced and
sometimes brought to panel in the school.
Once you're being caught like three
times in a missionary school stealing,
You're being expelled from the school.
Which some people has been expelled all for my sake.
Afterwards, I grew up with that
My parents in their hands
we're the best people that
ever happened to me.
They made sure I have
whatever I wanted.
Before the visiting
day they sent whatever I wanted,
such as 2 sets of provision.
But I would never eat it,
I kept it and take it home to them.
I didn't touch my provision.
Rather, I took from People,I never took mine.
I rather send mine back to my family.
When I take my girlfriend's provision,
I planted it in another person's bag.
My guardian in school, flogged me one day,
and I set her up too.
Because I didn't like someone correcting me.
Before I left Madona, something happened.
There was a day I went for clubbing
my parents never told me they were
visiting and it surprised me.
I was not in the school premises.
They called me, my girlfriend
never told me when she was returning,
she came back without my notice
and I was still in the campus in Okwa, Nnamdi azikiwe university.
Hanging out with those guys,
So when my parents called I returned back
when they had left and they were very angry
and the school punished me on that.
The only friend I called friend,
I could never hurt her,
but because of what she did and
my parents were angry with me,
I hurt her to the core.
When I left this school
that continues,
I could never respect you no
matter who you think you were
No one corrected me, but the only
person I listened to at times was my father.
My mother could not even stand me,
I insulted her and walk out of her.
I could only hear the voice of my father.
I didn't know why.
So I grew up with this, I was very good in making friends,
but I couldn't last with you in two days.
Highest I can last with a friend is just one week.
And we would have serious issues.
so this continued, I took from people and plant it in others,
so that the person would be embarrassed.
Recently, I didn't do that to people,
rather, I kept for myself.
The reason why the man of God
said I need to settle,
is because I'm not in good terms
with any of my friend or family.
I was meant to serve in Abuja,
but I left Abuja because of
what happened in the camp.
My very good friend,
the only good friend that stood by me,
the only girl that believed me.
That can worship me,
she would wash my clothes
and does everything for me.
On a sit out, I took her phone
switched it off, I even personally reported the case
to the camp commandant.
That I needed to find that phone,
because the camp commandant was my friend.
He went round in the whole camp,
searching the camp looking for that phone.
I was the hostel leader
I helped him to look for that phone
even in my own bag although It was inside my bag.
I opened my provision,
I put it inside the milk and sealed it back
Nobody could find it,
until when my brother came to visit me.
This is my brother.
All these continued, all my brothers
could never help me out,
ever since I started this.
But this my brother here was the only one that stood by me.
No matter what I did, he still pay my bills.
Whatever I wanted - to make sure I don't lack.
But there was something I did one day, and he beats me,
I got angry and vowed to destroy him.
Which is the only girl he ever loved.
I said a lot of things about him to the girl that
he is infected with disease.
That a girl should stay off.
I even tried to take the girl's phone to see if I can get a parents number,
But I couldn't.
I didn't know what else to do,
when I was in the camp I took that phone I sold it to him.
I wanted to give him what I told him,
"I don't have money you know I'm just a student,
give me money for the phone,"
I gave it to him.
And the person in question
happened to be my close friend, she's always in my house 24/7.
We eat together, she stay with my parents,
she enters my brother's room, they chat.
I knew definitely she's going to see the phone there.
I wished she caught him with the phone and embarrass him.
This my brother
He dealt with me seriously that day.
I never knew what came to me,
but then, they never knew what I was doing until now.
I tried to make him have a serious accident,
I tried to open his fuel tank,
but I don't know its always locked.
Bonnet, I can open it.
So what I did every early in the morning,
if my parents remember the dog
always back as early as four.
There is this particular knife, I always sleep with it.
I come out and punch the tires.
Whenever he is driving, he has a flat tire.
That continued, and one day my mum said,
"this quarrel you are having with your brother,
he is suspecting you that you
are the one punching his tires."
I didn't know where to hot damage his car,
I just wanted to see him pained,
because he gave me scratch in my body. -blood drops
I wanted his own blood to flow
that was why I wanted to do that.
But there was no way I could
plant anything into his car.
but to punch his tires.
That is what happened,
the last one that happened
my parents had to come over to bail me out.
And they told me, they will
never do it like that again.
This continued, but after this phone incident,
I was so ashamed of myself.
One other thing I did was,
When I sat out with a guy, he may see me and like me.
I was not interested in dating.
He can pass and see me and pack his car
to test me, my revenge would be to pick his phone,
take the number that I know
maybe his wife's number and save it.
Instead of sending you the text,
I would forward the text to her.
To the wife, "I'm waiting for you, where are you?"
so that she gets offended and you people have issues.
That is the only thing I did, just to make you feel bad.
And my sister here,
she's a very good person, she does business.
She sells men clothes.
But when I saw she was really moving up,
when I went to her house
and she was telling me that she has people
to meet - customers.
I would say, "very good,
let me wait for you,"
It hurt me when people turned my offer down.
She would tell me that she
wants to lock down her house
I would think, "is she feeling that
I want to steal her things?"
I would say okay,
where are you doing your supply?
And she would tell me where
she is going.
I would say, "Okay I'm off I'm going home."
either to my house or to my family house.
I'm very known so when I enter anywhere,
I will go and spoil that market for her.
Some people are even owing her,
They can't pay her anymore, all because of what I said.
I would make sure I give the number out to the wife,
I would look for the wife of that man and tell her.
"My sister is not selling clothes for your husband rather
she's busy sleeping with him."
Just to afflict pain on her and her business.
I just don't just like to see people. Happy.
Despite that, my family still stood by me.
Its the evil spirit in me, I was just a sadist.
I don't actually see me and husband together,
I am always alone.
I don't know why they would always stop me,
but I don't want to date them.
however, they keep pestering me,
so what I did was just to bring problem for them and go.
I caused them to have issues in their homes.
The truth is that, when I was in secondary school,
I was passing through things, and when my friends
introduced me to following men
and they would mess you up
and just leave you out.
I vowed, even still vows that
I would never want to get married,
But people kept coming.
That is why I didn't want to see anyone marrying.
None of my friend can open their mouth
and tell me they're getting married.
I would spoil that relationship.
If she tells me the guy,
I would tell her, "You have to watch
this guy very well, he is a womanizer."
Instead of me to encourage them.
Being her friend, She would take me to the guy's house,
Later. I would go back and spoil for her.
I would rather introduce her to another man,
and when she's with a man,
I would take photos of her and their conversation
and send it to the man that wants to get married to her.
And that's how they kept breaking up in their relationship.
{Can you see, why you should examine everything,
whatever you hear about your husband,
no matter how serious the issue is,
Whatever you hear about your wife,
no matter how serious the issue is.
You need to ask God.
You need to find out the truth
50% of the marriages today are divorced,
based on this fetish lie.
My father is a contractor
and he is will respected in my church.
But because of this, he hardly get any job,
people insult him in the public.
When he come back home,
he is always in tears.
When my father is sad, I ask him, "what is the problem?"
He wouldn't tell me
but later when he is scolding me,
he would mention it out.
Those that are owing him in the last job he did,
when he ask them for money,
they would say, "go and ask
your daughter to steal and give him."
So that has brought a lot of shame to the family,
Even my mom is even suffering from high blood pressure,
all because of me.
Those are the things that made me leave Abuja,
because I could not stand watching my family in shame.
I couldn't even walk on the streets,
my friends called me names.
Man of God all I ask is
for your help and to deliver me.
{How many year has this
spirit been tormenting you?}
Since I was in secondary school
I know all these things started in my JSS3
after I was given the post of the assistant regulator.
that is when I grew up with this,
(12- 15 years) now I have been with this.
But I can't control myself,
when things are being done
after like 30 minutes
I get myself back.
But there was no way I could
apologize to those people,
I would rather move on
{Since the Spirit of God fetched you out,
I will not allow you to go unless you are delivered.
Tell us what lesson you have?}
All I would say is that some times
Single-sex school is very bad,
female school is very bad
because you meet a lot of things.
Your school mother can keep
as a sex machine.
A lot of things goes on there,
either you can meet lesbians,
People who encourage you not to follow men,
rather you be with them.
Another one, I would always
advise my fellow girls and others.
Try to appreciate those who are happy
and be happy with them rejoice with
them and don't be a sadist.
Because right now, I am really regretting all my acts.
{You know, you have never
regretted like this before?}
No, I've never .
{To the extent of crying,
this is to tell you that the end has come.}
{I want to appeal to the family also
to a extend the hand of deliverance towards them,
and because I know the lady has affected
not only the society but the family.
She has affecting them negatively.
talk about the father or the brother or sister,
listen to what our sister has said.
It's a lesson to everyone of
us - big lesson.
May God help us!}
[We believe you have been inspired
by the clip you have just watched
click here to subscribe to witness more of
God's power at work in our generation today, and
stay up to date or the latest prophecies,
deliverance, sermons and testimonies from the Synagogue Church of All Nations
Emmanuel TV - changing lives, changing nations and change in the world]